Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cotton, Robert J. - I.D. - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Coughlin, Theresa - Copy of Ronald, Jr.,July 1, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Courser, Edwin - Baby,Christmas 1948 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Courtright, Val - Baby Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cowden, Kenneth,undated (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cowiser, Ed and Wife,December 14, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cox, Eli,undated (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cox, G.J.,undated (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives,3A-Gran, Coyne, Daniel G. - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cozat, Bonnie - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Craig, Clara L. - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crampton [no first name],undated (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crampton, Edwin,undated (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crane, Doris,undated (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crane, Emmitt,undated (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crane, G. (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crane, Lloyd - Baby Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crane, Lloyd - Wedding,undated (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crane, Pat - H.S.,undated (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crape, Robert,undated (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crapo, Ralph - Copy of Building,undated (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crawford, Elmer,undated (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crawford, Lea (Raseler),undated (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crowley, Dorothea - I.D. - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Crowley, Jim,undated (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cruz, James, Jr., Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Curtis, Delores,undated (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Curtis, S.L.,undated (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Curtis, Stou and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Curtiss, Glenn - Moose Lodge,April 4, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Curtiss, Richard - Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Cutler, Chas. - 9-month-old,December 16, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dad's Funeral - Francisco,undated (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dad's Funeral - Francisco - Old Man,undated (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dad's Funeral - Funeral Home - Francisco,undated (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dad's Funeral - Francisco - 2 Men,undated (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dale, R. E. - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Daley, Diane,undated (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Daley, Pat,undated (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dalrymple, Bill,April 4, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dammeyer, Karen,undated (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dana, Enid,August 1, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Danley, Dave,undated (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dargity, Darlene - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Darnell, Floyd,undated (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Darrow, Matthew - Couple,February 25, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dart, Ross - Baby Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davenport, Sharon,undated (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, David, Geraldine - Cap and Gown,undated (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, David, Robert,undated (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Cletus,undated (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Florence,undated (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Glen (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Gordon,undated (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, John,undated (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Lawrence (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Norma,undated (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Davis, Okla - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dawson, Bob - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dawson, J.,undated (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Day, W.S. (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dean, Zula (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DeBelle, M.H.,undated (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Decess, Homer,undated (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Decker, Geo. and Wife,April 5, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Decker, Glenn E. - Copy of Birth Registration for Lorraine Blanche Decker,undated (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deer Hunter,1939 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deer Hunting - Harrison and Rocky,1941 (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deer Hunting,1949 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DeFay,James,undated (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Degard, Cy and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DeGrand, Madelin (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dehn, Douglas,June 28, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deibel, Florence (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deihl, Ed - Copy of Soldier,undated (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deihl, Ed and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deihl, Gertrude (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Delick, Mike - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dell, Barbara,March 28, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dell, Ernest,undated (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Delo, A.E.,undated (Box 4, Folder 407)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Delong, Barbara - 5.5-month-old Girl,August 4, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 408)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Delong, Carol,undated (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Delong, Nola,undated (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Delong, Walt - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Demis, Tom,undated (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Demlow, Ronald,October 7, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DeMoines, David - Couple,undated (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DeMoines, David - Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Demski, George,undated (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Demski, Rose,undated (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Deni, Luige,undated (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dennis, Shirley,October 7, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Denslow, Glee - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Denslow, L.,undated (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dent, Gerald,undated (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dent, Mabel,March 28, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dent, Rodney,undated (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Derry, Jack,undated (Box 4, Folder 425)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Desormes, Robert - Wife - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 426)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Detiviler, Garold,undated (Box 4, Folder 427)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Detiviler, Garold - Baby Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 428)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Detiviler, Garold, Sir.undated (Box 4, Folder 429)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Detiviler, Garold - 5- and 7- year-old girls,undated (Box 4, Folder 430)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DeVaney, F. and Wife,October 10, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 431)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dexter, [no first name] (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 432)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Diamond, Wm., Dr.,November 25, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 433)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dibble, Danny - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 434)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dibble, John - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dibble, Tom,Decmeber 27, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 436)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dibble, Tonnie,undated (Box 4, Folder 437)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dickinson, Terry and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 438)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dierkes, N. - 6-month-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 439)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dingman, Howard (Mr.) - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 440)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dingman, Lois,undated (Box 4, Folder 441)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doebring, Ed,undated (Box 4, Folder 442)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doerfer, Eldon - Wedding,undated (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doerfer, Ellen,undated (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doerfer, Violet,undated (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doherty, Erma - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 446)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doherty, Leo F.,undated (Box 4, Folder 447)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Don, Stanley - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 448)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Donahue, Glen - Twin to Corcoran, Pat,undated (Box 4, Folder 449)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Donald, Bertha - Cap and Gown,undated (Box 4, Folder 450)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Donald, E.P. (Mrs.) - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 451)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Donald, John,undated (Box 4, Folder 452)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Donald, Loretta,undated (Box 4, Folder 453)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Doty, B.L.,undated (Box 4, Folder 454)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dowell, Al - H.S.,undated (Box 4, Folder 455)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dowell, Dick,undated (Box 4, Folder 456)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dowell, Jason,undated (Box 4, Folder 457)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dowell, Ray - H.S.,undated (Box 4, Folder 458)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Draper, Rosie Fairchild,undated (Box 4, Folder 459)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Dressler, Jeanne - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 460)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Duddles, Jim,undated (Box 4, Folder 461)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Duddles, Linda,undated (Box 4, Folder 462)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Duguay, Mary Edama,undated (Box 4, Folder 463)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, DuLai, Ivan,undated (Box 4, Folder 464)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Durfee, Art,July 26, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 465)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Durham, Rollie,undated (Box 4, Folder 466)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Earl's Funeral,undated (Box 4, Folder 467)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Earl, Don,undated (Box 4, Folder 468)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Earl, Richard - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 469)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Earns, Harry,undated (Box 4, Folder 470)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ebuilt, Ilah - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 471)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ebuit, Sharlene - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 472)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eckert, Martha - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 473)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eckert, Roberta,undated (Box 4, Folder 474)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Economan, Wm. - two girls,undated (Box 4, Folder 475)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Edmonds, Robert- Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 476)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Egbert, C.E.,undated (Box 4, Folder 477)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ege, Anthony and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 478)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ege, Joanne,undated (Box 4, Folder 479)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ehle, Thelma - H.S.,undated (Box 4, Folder 480)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eismann, Nancy,1961 (Box 4, Folder 481)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eismann, Nancy - High School, Engagement,undated (Box 4, Folder 482)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eismann, Nancy - Vic Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 483)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eismann, Vic - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 484)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Eldred, Gladys, M. - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 485)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Elliot, Lanson - couple,undated (Box 4, Folder 486)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Elliott, Ken - Moose Lodge,undated (Box 4, Folder 487)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Elliott, Robert - 2-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 488)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Elliott, Warren,undated (Box 4, Folder 489)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ellis, Fern E.,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 490)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ellison, Roy,undated (Box 4, Folder 491)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Emory, Marjorie - Baby,undated (Box 4, Folder 492)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Emory, Marjory,undated (Box 4, Folder 493)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Endres, Gladys Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 494)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Engelhardt, Devere,August 24, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 495)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Engler, John (Mrs.) - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 496)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Engler, Matt (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 497)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, English, Duane - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 498)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Epple, Dolores Pohl,undated (Box 4, Folder 499)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Epple, Ed,undated (Box 4, Folder 500)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Epple, Jim,undated (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ercole, Noble,undated (Box 4, Folder 502)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ervans, Eugene,undated (Box 4, Folder 503)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ervin, Effie,undated (Box 4, Folder 504)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ervin, Larry,undated (Box 4, Folder 505)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ervin, Robt.,July 29, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 506)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Erwin, Ronald,undated (Box 4, Folder 507)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Esch, Delton,undated (Box 4, Folder 508)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Esch, Lewis - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 509)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Esch, Lewis and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 510)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Esch, Lynn,undated (Box 4, Folder 511)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Evans, L.,February 9, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 512)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Faber, E.,undated (Box 4, Folder 513)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Faber, Richard - 1-year-old,July 24, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 514)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Faber, William and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 515)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fabiano, Erdine,undated (Box 4, Folder 516)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fabiano, Joe,undated (Box 4, Folder 517)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fair, Roland,undated (Box 4, Folder 518)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fair, Roy - Wedding (Myrtle Alexander),October 15, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 519)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fairchild, Vernon,undated (Box 4, Folder 520)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fallon, Mike,undated (Box 4, Folder 521)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fallon, Pete,undated (Box 4, Folder 522)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fallon, Tim,undated (Box 4, Folder 523)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Falsetta, Sam,undated (Box 4, Folder 524)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Farmer, J. - Baby Boy,undated (Box 4, Folder 525)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Farnan, Gerald,undated (Box 4, Folder 526)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Favreau, Sylvia,undated (Box 4, Folder 527)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fedewa, Ed. - 1st Communion - Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 528)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fedewa, Ed. - 4 Children,undated (Box 4, Folder 529)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Feltman, [no first name] - Copy of Family Group,undated (Box 4, Folder 530)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Feltman, Martha,undated (Box 4, Folder 531)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Feltman, Rose Marie,undated (Box 4, Folder 532)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ferris, Chas. - Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 533)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ferris, Ed.,June 22, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 534)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ferrison, Audry,undated (Box 4, Folder 535)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fetterly, Dorothy,June 22, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 536)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Filbin, John,undated (Box 4, Folder 537)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Findley, Walt,undated (Box 4, Folder 538)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Finnerty, Robert - 6-month-old,January 11, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 539)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Finnerty, Robt. - 8-month-old Girl ,undated (Box 4, Folder 540)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Finnerty, Robert (2),August 7, 1965, August 30, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 541)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Finnerty, Robert. - 8-month-old,December 7, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 542)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Finney, May - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 543)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Finney, Paul,undated (Box 4, Folder 544)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fish [a dead fish],1949 (Box 4, Folder 545)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fish, Chad - Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 546)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fish, Eunice,undated (Box 4, Folder 547)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fish, Georgia - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 548)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fish, Joyce,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 549)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fish, Ray,undated (Box 4, Folder 550)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fisher, Helen - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 551)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fishing,undated (Box 4, Folder 552)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fishing - Three Men,May 1, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 553)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fishing Trip - Three Men,May 5, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 554)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fitzgerald, Ed - Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 555)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fitzgerald, Floyd - 50th Anniversary,January 17, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 556)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fitzgibbons, Ellen,undated (Box 4, Folder 557)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fitzpatrick, Jim - 2.5-month-old Boy,undated (Box 4, Folder 558)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fitzpatrick, J. - Group of Five,undated (Box 4, Folder 559)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flannery, Bob - 2-year-old Boy,undated (Box 4, Folder 560)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flannery, Bob - Wedding,undated (Box 4, Folder 561)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flannery, Bob - 1-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 562)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flannery, Rome and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 563)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flaugher, Elmer,August 30, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 564)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flaugher, Mrs, Elmer (Elizabeth),undated (Box 4, Folder 565)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flaugher, Geo.,undated (Box 4, Folder 567)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flaugher, Glen - Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 568)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flaugher, Ron - Mrs. - Drums - Passport,March 13, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 569)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flood, Wayne,undated (Box 4, Folder 570)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Floria, Dawn,undated (Box 4, Folder 571)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fluharty, Harold - Family -Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 571)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fluharty, Jack, H.S.,undated (Box 4, Folder 572)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flynn, Orm - Whit Lake - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 573)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flynn, Orman - Soldier,undated (Box 4, Folder 574)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Flynn, Robert,undated (Box 4, Folder 575)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Folty, Frank,undated (Box 4, Folder 576)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Foltz, Judy,undated (Box 4, Folder 577)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Foltz, Russell - Honorable Discharge,December 24, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 578)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Ford, Fred,undated (Box 4, Folder 579)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Forney, Mabel,undated (Box 4, Folder 580)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Forney, Mabel - I.D.,March 28, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 581)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Forney, Sam (Mrs.),undated (Box 4, Folder 582)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fortner, Clarence - Birth Certificate of Lois Ann Fortner,October 2, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 583)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fortner, Clarence - Birth Certificate of Walter John Fortner,September 5, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 584)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Foster, Dick,undated (Box 4, Folder 585)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fox, Ed and Wife - Passport,undated (Box 4, Folder 586)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fox, Herman - 1.5-year-old Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 587)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fox, James,undated (Box 4, Folder 588)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fox, Mary,undated (Box 4, Folder 589)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fox, Mutt,February 10, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 590)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fox, Steve and Wife,October 3, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 591)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco, Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 592)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family,undated (Box 4, Folder 593)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Army Soldier,undated (Box 4, Folder 594)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Baby,undated (Box 4, Folder 595)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family Baby,1930 (Box 4, Folder 596)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Couple,undated (Box 4, Folder 597)